credit-land.com 2016-11-30

# Privacy Statement - Credit-Land.com

## Privacy Statement of Credit-Land.com

**Introduction**

Credit-Land.com, Inc. ("we" or "us") values its visitors' privacy. This Privacy Statement describes how we treat information we might collect from any visitor ("you").

Please note that this Privacy Statement does not govern the collection and use of information by companies that Credit-Land.com, Inc. does not control, nor by individuals not employed or managed by Credit-Land.com, Inc.

**Personal information we collect**

We collect information from and about you. It is always up to you whether to disclose personal information to us. We may ask you to submit personal information like your name and email address. We may also ask whether you have a bank account, declared bankruptcy, and we may ask your credit score.

**Other information we collect**

We may collect other information that cannot be readily used to identify you, such as (for example) the domain name and IP address of your computer. We may use this information, individually or in the aggregate, for technical administration of Credit-Land.com; research and development; and to help us focus our marketing efforts more precisely.

**How we use it**

We use information in many ways. We will:

  * use information to respond to your questions;
  * use information to improve our website and services or customize your experience with us;
  * use information for marketing purposes. For example, we use information we know about you to offer you relevant information, services and products;
  * use information as otherwise permitted by law. We will keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Privacy Statement. We will also keep information as otherwise required by law;
  * take commercially reasonable precautions to protect the information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction;
  * not sell or rent information to a third party without your permission;
  * not use or disclose the information except: 
    * as required by law, for example, in response to a subpoena or search warrant;
    * as necessary to protect the rights, safety, or property of Credit-Land.com, Inc., its users, or others; this may include (for example) exchanging information with other organizations for fraud protection and/or risk reduction.

**Cookies**

Credit-Land.com, Inc. uses technologies such as cookies and pixel tags. We use cookies to store personal data on your computer. We may also link information stored on your computer in cookies with personal data about specific individuals stored on our servers. We use pixel tags to learn how you use our services.

**External data storage**

We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.

**We use standard security measures**

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access, we use security measures that comply with federal law, including computer safeguards. However, the Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of Credit-Land.com will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet.

**Credit-Land.com may link to third party services that we don't control.**

If you click on a link to a third-party site, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This includes social media sites. This Privacy Statement does not apply to the privacy practices of these websites. Carefully read the privacy policy of other websites. We are not responsible for these third party practices.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy as we deem necessary or appropriate. We will post an updated copy at Credit-Land.com. Please check periodically for updates.

**Questions or comments?**

If you have questions or comments about Credit-Land.com, Inc.'s privacy policy, contact us via any of the ways described in the Contact Us page.

We look forward to servicing you online!
